<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Medscape2.0</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="splash_top_txt">Perfect \nWaste\nManagement</string>
    <string name="medscape">Medscape</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log in</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="hello">hello</string>

    <!--    errors-->
    <string name="empty_error">Field must not be empty</string>
    <string name="email_error">Must be a valid email</string>
    <string name="pass_error">Must contain Capital and Non-Capital letters, Number, Special character and Minimum length of 8</string>
    <string name="mobile_short_error">Mobile number must be 10 digits</string>
    <string name="mobile_error">Mobile number must be valid</string>
    <string name="name_short_error">Name should be 3 digits</string>
    <string name="name_error">Name should be valid with only alphabet characters</string>

    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="mobile">Mobile</string>
    <string name="permission_request_deny_message">This app needs the Location permission to show your current location on the map. \n\nNOTE: If after clicking OK, this message shows again, grant the location permission from App settings of Medscape.</string>
    <string name="location_permission_dialog_title">Location Permission Needed</string>
    <string name="center_marker">center marker</string>
    <string name="direction">direction</string>
    <string name="done_button">done_button</string>
    <string name="this_app_need_camera_permission_for_capturing_photos_from_camera">This app need camera permission for capturing photos from camera. \n\nNOTE: If after clicking OK, this message shows again, grant the location permission from App settings of Medscape.</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_needed">Camera permission needed</string>
    <string name="profile_photo">Profile photo</string>
    <string name="camera_button">camera button</string>
    <string name="camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="gallery_button">gallery button</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="set_avater_button">set avater button</string>
    <string name="your_avatar">your avatar</string>
    <string name="back_button">back button</string>
    <string name="choose_your_profile_pic">Choose your profile pic</string>
    <string name="your_photo_is_used_to_identify_you_nduring_garbage_collection">Your photo is used to identify you \nduring garbage collection</string>
    <string name="user_already_registered">You are already registered, kindly Sign in.</string>
    <string name="internal_server_error">Something went wrong</string>
    <string name="empty_avatar_error">Select a profile photo to continue</string>
    <string name="login_invalid_creadential_error">Incorrect email or password</string>
    <string name="could_not_get_address">Could not get address</string>
    <string name="address_not_found">Address not found</string>
    <string name="content">Some Firebase Authentication methods that take email addresses as parameters throw specific errors if the email address is unregistered when it must be registered (for example, when signing in with an email address and password), or registered when it must be unused (for example, when changing a user\'s email address). While this can be helpful for suggesting specific remedies to users, it can also be abused by malicious actors to discover the email addresses registered by your users.\n\nTo mitigate this risk, we recommend you enable email enumeration protection for your project using the Google Cloud gcloud tool. Note that enabling this feature changes Firebase Authentication\'s error reporting behavior: be sure your app doesn\'t rely on the more specific errors.\n\nNext steps\nAfter a user signs in for the first time, a new user account is created and linked to the credentials—that is, the user name and password, phone number, or auth provider information—the user signed in with. This new account is stored as part of your Firebase project, and can be used to identify a user across every app in your project, regardless of how the user signs in.\n\nIn your apps, the recommended way to know the auth status of your user is to set an observer on the Auth object. You can then get the user\'s basic profile information from the User object. See Manage Users.\n\nIn your Firebase Realtime Database and Cloud Storage Security Rules, you can get the signed-in user\'s unique user ID from the auth variable, and use it to control what data a user can access.\n\nYou can allow users to sign in to your app using multiple authentication providers by linking auth provider credentials to an existing user account.\n\nTo sign out a user, call signOut:</string>
</resources>